With the 18th pick in the 2026 NFL
draft, the Minnesota Vikings select,
Caleb Banks, defensive end, Florida.
>> All right, I'll give you the floor. I'm
allowed. Yeah, he's my 51st player. I
mean, there is a ton of ability there,
but he's had an injury with his foot. He
reinjured it. Didn't get to see him much
this year. [cheering]
So, someone who only played three games
this year, he's a flash player. It's a
little bit hot and cold, but when you
see that on the screen, 66 [cheering]
and a/4, you see that size at 327
lbs with 35 in arms. I mean, this is a
swing for the fences. If you hit on this
one, you could end up with an all pro
cuz he's got all that ability. It's just
there's not a lot of games to go off of,
and it's a little bit up and down in
terms of the consistency. But when you
watch the tape, you want to get excited
about him. You're a Vikings fan. You see
him at his best, you cannot move him. He
uses those 35 in arms. [music] He locks
out blockers and you can't move him.
Another example of him against the run.
He's going to reset the line [music] of
scrimmage. He's just too big and long
and powerful. And then these are the
flashes you see particularly in this
game. This was the one against LSU where
you can see him get on edges and work up
the field. Wanted to see this a more
consistent version of this power to
collapse the pocket because it's all in
his body. It's all there. It's just a
little bit of a this is a boomer guy.
You're going to hit it big or it's not
going to work out. But they swung for
the fences here in